Correct! aboutş Monster
Negiko Negi-chan Neru
Yillas
Hi, I'm Miu Fujitani.
I'm Hikaru Ritsuki.
and We'll be answering your questions today.
You want to answer?
We've recruited a lot of people.
Do you want to answer?
It's my first time.
It's the first time.
I've never seen you before.
I'm Kokoromi, right?
First time Kokoromi channel
Kokoromi channel
Hagukumi
Hagukumi Channel
Mi-chan, I'll answer your questions
I've asked for answers from everyone.
There are a lot of questions.
Yeah...
The episode that made you think you're a magical girl.
Mi-chan will answer that.
That's right.
But I think you've always been a magical girl.
Yes, yes, yes.
I especially thought that...
The way you use words too.
Yes.
Yes, but when you're sad, for example...
But when you're sad, for example... well, in the human world, it's like...
I think that kind of thinking is possible in Puella Magi 7.
I guess so. Thank you.
I'll see you again.
Please look at the camera and talk as members without opening your mouth.
Without opening your mouth?
What do you mean?
Oh, I mean this.
Like this?
Yeah.
Okay, let's just do this for the first part of the show.
Okay, okay.
I'm really good at this.
I'm good at this.
Oh, I know.
I'm good at this. - Okay.
Where did you come from?
I know.
Oh, you'll be surprised.
Yeah, I'm good at that.
I'll pick the most pampered member.
Whoa!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Aah!
Uh... uh...
Pampered?
That's a tough one.
But I'm...
I'm spoiled by society.
Oh, you're a pampered child?
For this situation.
So do you, squid.
But...
You and Yunuchan are different.
But Ika is something like that.
I don't know.
Are you mad at me?
Yeah.
It's like... when I come here, if I get cut off, I'm like...
I'm sure. - Yeah.
Like that.
Yes, that's true.
But if you think about it from a spoiled girl's point of view...
I think Mimi-chan has a lot of it.
Me?
Yes.
Really?
Really.
They're kind of cute.
Don't let anyone spoil you.
I don't do nyan-nyan.
Maybe not.
Yeah.
There's a lot of each.
Yes, sir.
And so on.
But does it depend on her?
For Hikaru, yes. For Hikaru-chan.
But it depends on the person.
Yes, it does.
What's the temperature of your air conditioner?
Uh...
27.8 degrees.
Wow, that's high.
Air conditioning?
I don't know... I'm really cold.
I'm a cold person.
I don't like the wind from the air conditioner. It makes me cold.
But in the summer, people are always burning up the backstage area.
I understand.
Set the temperature to 19 degrees Celsius.
19 degrees. 19 degrees.
That's why people don't notice.
It's like...
Oh, you're doing it for them?
I'm giving it to them, and then after a while...
It's kind of hot.
It's like, "Why is it going up so high?
I'm 23 degrees, it's not cold, it's cold, it's cold, why do you want to go up again?
How did this happen?
This,
Common sense dictates.
Really,
The truth is..,
I was originally yellow-green.
This color.
But something changed,
He was light blue,
pink,
Light blue was given away,
Light blue was given over to light blue,
He went light blue.
What did you like?
I liked the yellow-green.
You liked it?
Even now.
Yes, I still like it.
You like yellow-green?
I like yellow-green too.
But it's because I'm making it easier to eat my light blue skinny personality.
If it were yellowish-green, I'd probably be a different character.
What do you mean?
I'd have a little more of a cleaning persona.
I'm playing cleanup now.
Oh, yeah.
Are you baby pink, Yu-chan?
Yeah.
That's the color.
Yes, it is.
Oh, it's showing.
It's out.
The stone came out.
I like baby pink.
You like baby pink, right?
Which one of you would rather play with a 5 year old or a 5 year old?
You want to say all of them?
Ei-kun has already decided.
The 5 year old will be with the 5 people, right?
Let's say they stay together for a day.
Okay, I'll do it.
Isn't it too hard?
What? It's a no-brainer.
Seriously?
From the moment I saw it.
Oh, I'm so torn.
It bothers me a lot.
Okay.
If I was a mother of five...
No, I'm not.
Five?
Mother of five.
I don't know.
I don't know. I've never met her.
I don't know, I've never met her, but she makes me do crazy things.
I get the feeling...
Yeah. - Yeah.
I just felt like I was gonna get my skirt ripped up or something.
I felt like he was gonna rip my skirt off or something.
Do you do that now?
I was just wondering if it was an exaggeration of what you would do now.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I'm sure it is.
Scary.
A little scary.
Scary in a good way
Definitely 5-year-old Kaede!
Come here.
I see what you mean.
That's for sure.
She's absolutely adorable.
Absolutely adorable.
That's the time.
Good night.
I wish I had met the members when they were babies.
I wish I was a baby.
Wouldn't that be nice? Which is it, guys?
Which is it?
I want you to tell me about a long, cute case that only the members know about.
Only the members know.
One cute one, one cute one.
Sis, when you need a little advice...
What do you mean by "consulting"? Like, when you have to say something cute or something.
Like, when there's a project, you know, where everyone's around...
Are you sure? And then you call them up and make a comment.
You know, like a comment.
And then they would go up to the rooftop to check on us.
Microphone all the way up to the roof.
There were times when it was like a really cute line from Pacifico.
It was like I had to say something really cute.
You don't remember what you did? I don't know. My memory's kind of blown.
I said something that was probably pretty shocking.
It was like on Blu-ray.
I have a little bit of talent.
That's it.
And...
I don't know...
When you ask me out...
I'll say...
"Rin-chan, are you free today?
And then...
"Do you have plans after this?
Like that.
First of all, just spontaneously.
Not like, "Where are you going?
Is there anything else after this?
Like, nothing at all?
I mean...
I'm just trying to get to the bottom of it.
Are you hungry? Or, like...
Oh, my God.
I'll ask him out. He'll tell me.
I'm really bad at asking people out.
I know what you mean.
Tell me you don't have bad feelings for him. He makes me feel great.
That's what I'm doing.
But I'm glad you're asking me out so much.
There you go.
That's what I think of Rin.
First of all, the stamps you have are cute
The stamps you have are cute
You have a lot of stamps
First of all, the stamps you have are cute.
I wonder... if it's her cute side.
Or the poems.
It's so cute.
It's hard to say.
You mean all of them?
There's a little wording in the poem.
Like "somehow" instead of "somehow.
Not "something" but "something".
I think that kind of grammar is cute.
That's nice, that's nice, that's nice.
I find that cute.
I'm glad.
I like the way you use words...
Nikkoi Channel
wow, all square balls
Pinkle.
Shhh mah?
Yes, that's right.
Is it okay?
We're not fighting, are we?
I get a lot of people asking if we're gonna fight.
Oh, they come a lot?
He's been coming a lot.
What?
No, I don't.
And maybe I'll fight with the staff.
I'm coming.
Oh, you will?
Yes, I do.
I don't fight.
I don't mean fight.
It's more like...
Argument?
Not really an argument, more of a genuine disagreement.
I see.
But... But...
There were times when he wouldn't listen to me, and I'd say, "Ugh.
I just left.
I just said, "That's enough." I left. Wow. That's great.
Can you tell us about your plans for the future? Sure.
Okay, then? Yourself?
What?
Your life plan for the future? Uh, well, you know.
I'm thinking about getting a bob in a couple of years. I'm looking forward to it.
You sent me a picture of me with a bob in the middle of the night.
I sent him a bunch of stuff.
A lot of stuff.
I can do it in my own way.
I can do it in my own way. I can do a bob.
I sent it to Rin-chan, who sent me a lot of pictures.
It looked good on you. But I knew it would look good on you.
But I want it in a couple of years. I have a sense of foresight. A couple of years? Yeah, a few years.
And don't you think it's a little embarrassing? Without hair. No, I know.
You don't have anything to hide? I want to live like this.
I know, I know.
This is how you walk. I know.
You walk like this on the train.
I walk like this all the time. I'd be worried if it wasn't here.
I have a hair that I haven't reached that point yet...
Roo-chan wants to have pink hair.
I like it. I want you to do it.
I don't care if it's this color right now.
Yes, that's good.
Great, great.
What do you want to be in your next life?
I'm not really interested.
I want to disappear in this life, soul and all.
I want to be gone in this life.
I want to end it all in this life of light.
I see.
Your favorite.
Why is that?
I don't know.
You said you wanted to be food.
I think it's better to have a quickie than a longie.
I mean, I could disappear at any time.
I think it would be better if it ends with a delicious meal.
With okonomiyaki, there's the process of making it.
I wonder if there is a will there.
Yes, so I've thought about it right away.
If you were to change from powder to flour, for example, you would drop a little bit before turning into flour, right?
So, you would make okonomiyaki, and then your life would be over.
The okonomiyaki is a mixture of various things, and it becomes okonomiyaki, right?
The finished product is the ideal.
You're right, the carrots would be too thin.
And then there's this iced green onion.
Cabbage, lettuce...
Around there.
Then mayonnaise, so we can pour it on top.
Okay.
I'll go with mayonnaise.
I like mayonnaise.
Can any of you do a three-pointed stand?
Yes, we do.
More or less.
I used to be able to.
Oh, yes?
Yes.
There was a comedian named Samiko Nishioka.
You know how she's been doing it for three years?
I might know.
And, yeah, that's kind of difficult.
I watched her a lot.
I liked her. And I imitated her a lot.
It's funny? I was doing it.
Oh, my God.
That's good.
You said you were going to show me something.
Already done. Already done.
Here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
If you see one, say "wow".
Okay.
Maybe I'm reading too fast.
Really?
I can't keep up.
You read really fast?
Speed-reading.
I didn't think about that.
I thought you were looking for something.
Oh, is that what this is about?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm reading it all really fast.
I read too fast.
I used to speed read.
Yeah, I read really fast.
He said he was learning how to read.
Oh, that's great.
How do you learn to read?
Yes! He said.
Speed reading?
What's that, huh?
It's like, "Pow, pow, pow" on the screen.
You know what a flash-and-read is?
Uh...
Speed reading.
It's like when you get 20 minutes of a live broadcast and then you ask for the last minute, and it's like, "Papa, papa, papa, papa, papa.
I mean, you read, like, a symbol or something.
You answer.
Like, "Yes, what is it?" I just do it on the computer, and it's great.
It's great. It's really helpful.
I've never done it before, but you're really fast.
I don't know why, but she says she can't lose.
I don't know why...
Cute episodes?
The part where he plays with his socks...
I see...
I'm right there.
That captain is really funny because he tries to play with fashion with his socks.
Usually when we have live shows or when the staff wears black.
So, why not just wear black socks with fluorescent socks?
Purple, red...
You know, there are a lot of guys like that on the staff.
There are guys who only wear socks with fruit patterns on them.
I heard that yesterday. Why are you playing with socks? Like, "Why are you trying to play with my socks?
He asked me to play with them.
He said he wants to play.
What do you mean?
Is it?
I don't know. I thought it was cute. I thought, "Why can't he learn?
But there was this obsessive live show.
And every year we drop the captain in the pool.
But every year he doesn't bring a change of clothes.
So you didn't bring a change of clothes this year either.
But you drop him, of course.
It's a given that you'll drop it.
We don't drop ours.
So I asked him why he didn't laugh.
I asked him why he didn't laugh. Then he said because we're all grown up now, he doesn't do that anymore.
Every year I think about it, but every year they drop me.
That's why I think it's cute.
I think it's cute.
Oh, is this good?
It's good, it's good.
I want to say I don't like it. I want to say I'm a singer.
Okay. - Okay.
You want to say it, don't you?
What do you want to say?
You want to say it?
Yes, I do.
Yes, sir.
I'd like to know the members' playlists.
Yes, please.
Say out loud your favorite artist.
Spirits.
Yes, out loud, please.
Yes, I'll go.
Yes, ma'am.
Amagic.
Yes, sir.
I heard you in the comment section.
Is that all you listen to?
No, but I listen to a lot of stuff.
But I do.
It's what suits me at the time.
Some of Ome Shape's songs fit better than others.
I've been listening to it today too.
How would you compare yourself to oden?
Often.
I've been called "image oden".
I'm often told that I'm "hanpen".
People say Karu-chan looks like a hanpen.
I'm told that Karu-chan looks like a hanpen.
I can't eat hanpen.
I see.
But I've told her about that before.
I can't eat hanpen, but
But that probably means it's white.
I said, "That's fine.
It's okay to say that.
It's fluffy. It's comfortable to the touch.
So it's okay.
I said, "That's fine.
I think I'm an icon.
Icons have some kind of stain on them, don't they?
Maybe I'm soaked.
You absorb a lot of things.
Yes, yes, yes.
The colors are getting darker and darker every day.
That's great.
You're growing deeper and deeper, aren't you?
But I'm feeling it too.
Yes.
I've been trying to become a deeper person in the past year.
I'm so happy.
I'm glad.
I want to hold hands with my boyfriend, but I don't have the courage. What should I do?
He's so cute.
Isn't he cute?
Yes, it is.
I think...
You should start with a hand massage.
No, you do it.
Come on.
I'm embarrassed.
I'm embarrassed by all the people.
I'm really embarrassed.
Let's try it after all.
Okay, go ahead.
Okay, I'll try it.
Your hands are kind of stiff, aren't they?
Hands?
Yeah.
One time.
Please.
This is the point for potato wood.
How's that?
It hurts.
Does it hurt?
This is a pressure point on the head.
It's not good.
Here's what I'm going to do.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Yeah, it's cute.
How's it look? It's good.
That's what I'm talking about.
It's good.
I like the last combination.
But I really think this is the point of an immortal tie.
Oh, here?
Heh.
So you can press here for the pressure points on the ymotai.
Got it.
Here's a pressure point for waking up, and there's an automatic pressure point.
I did it.
Oh, like this?
Yeah.
What's the most fun part of a live show?
When you're all looking at each other and the band members.
Eye contact.
When you're having fun, when everyone's having fun.
Everyone, the members?
Everyone?
Members?
I am?
When I'm having a really good time.
Yeah. - Yeah.
But there's a lot of fun.
I love it when they come on live, every time I see them.
I know, I know.
Everything gives you goosebumps.
I know. I know.
No matter how many times they appear.
I know.
If you were standing next to me?
I'd still get goosebumps.
The members?
Yeah.
And if they say "wow," I get goosebumps, too.
I love the way they come on.
Pasiric.
I got goosebumps when I saw that.
Oh, my God.
Open it.
Ummm.
the one with the...
OK, OK.
So, when I went to the waist last year.
I came out with that Tenichi, and you know, I love the silhouette hips.
I couldn't stop getting goosebumps then.
I couldn't stop goosebumps.
Even you?
Myself.
I can't stop.
You do?
Maybe that's what I'll end up like.
Don't you want to see it?
I don't want to see it.
Yes, sir.
If you were to write one kanji character for each member, what would it be?
Let's see...
Hm? Can't you say "Se-de"?
Okay, I'll say "Se-de".
Okay, I'll say it.
Let's start with you, Arun-chan.
Okay.
Sparse.
Thank you.
Bye, Arne-chan.
Yes, ma'am.
Se-no bi... ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
It's fun. You know what I'm saying? Okay, okay, okay.
It's how you go, isn't it? Where you look?
Yes, where to look
Yes, yes
Ready, sound!
What is that? What is that? A pond?
A pond?
Yeah, it's kind of cool.
Oh, that way.
Yeah. - Yeah.
I thought it was a pond.
A pond?
Oh, a pond?
That's not a pond.
No, it's not.
You believe that?
Yeah, I do.
Okay. - Okay.
Okay.
Let's go, Tabiyaka!
You know, just in case.
Yes.
Karen?
Wow, this is hard!
It's obvious. Is it obvious? It's a little difficult.
Okay, okay. Ready, horse.
What's it gonna be? Horse? Horse? I think it's a horse.
Yeah, it's got to die. I don't know. I wonder how this one's gonna go.
Let's see how this one goes.
Come on, come on, come on, come on...
You want to be yourself?
No, no, no, please don't.
Please don't.
Okay, okay, okay.
Yes!
By yourself?
Yeah, yeah.
Ready!
Daddy kiss.
Okay, okay.
Okay, yes.
Hey, cutie. - Yeah.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
God's all here.
Well, it's all here.
All right, all right, all right.
That's good.
But of course, God is all here.
It's all there if you think about it.
What's the word you often use?
Before we go live, we use the engine.
"Gabridges" on the engine before we go live.
I'm addicted to it.
When I think about it, I just keep saying it.
I thought it was cute.
It's so funny.
"Gabridges is...
I just kept saying it.
It just hit the nail on the head.
You know...
Gabridge is...
I say it all the time.
I say, "I'll do my best when I want to do my best.
Is this what you've been doing lately?
What's your 50m time?
50 meters is like 9 seconds?
Like 9 seconds?
Maybe... maybe 9 seconds.
Not fast?
Is it fast? I did it in like 12 seconds.
Not 100?
What? What?
Really?
But I used to fall at the start.
That's why you quit?
Yeah, that's why I quit.
That was my life.
How do you keep going even when things get bad?
Even if you think you can't do it anymore...
But before you know it, you're trying.
Over and over again.
I think I know what you mean.
I really tell people this.
I don't really recommend it to people I don't recommend it to
And those who stick with me, they stick with me.
I don't mean to sound like a dringa-dringa-dringa-dringa-dringa-dringa.
I like to say that I don't have a choice.
I'm with you.
Yeah.
Well, that word has saved my life.
It's saved my life.
I think "it can't be helped" is a magic word.
If you say "I have no choice", then anything is possible
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes
No choice
I'll ask you a question.
Yes.
Yes...
Why is the rice on the bottom of sushi?
There's no point in thinking about it.
It's because the rice is on the bottom of the sushi.
If you say it can't be helped, you can do whatever you want.
It's easy to give up, but you have to accept it.
It can't be helped.
But when I get over this, I'll be able to raise the level of my life, so I'll do my best.
Yes, that's right.
I hope he's okay. Bye-bye. Bye-bye.
What if he eats it?
And what if he eats this at the end?
So that's it...
That's the end of the Smile Channel. Thank you very much. What do you think?
I think you came here today so that you could understand what's going on.
I don't know what it's all about.
I don't know what it's all about, but we talked about things that we don't talk about very often, and it was a lot of fun.
But it was really fun to talk about things that we don't talk about very much.
I'm glad you enjoyed it.
Let's talk again.
I would have liked to have had a more in-depth conversation.
Let's have something to eat next time.
But I don't know if we can do that if we have two things going on.
You can't do two things.
It's hard to do two things.
But you can dance and sing.
That's right. How can you sing and dance at the same time?
Do you know what I mean?
Correct.
Yes. Then how do I finish?
Okay, thank you very much.
Okay. - What?
What? How do I show you?
Okay, okay.
Okay. Thank you very much.
It's done! It's done!
We're in it together, but we'll be exposed.
Oh, no.
Bye, bye, bye.
Please subscribe to our channel.